Jean Sovatkin Picker papers, 1915-1988
Sophia Smith Collection
Jean Picker papers
1915-1988
Picker, Jean S.
121
37 (18.5 linear ft.)
Sophia Smith Collection Smith College Northampton, MA
The Jean Picker papers consist of 18.5 linear feet and are primarily related to her professional and public life, dating from 1968-86. Types of material include correspondence, speeches, photographs, articles, reports, minutes, publicity, transcripts of interviews, invitations, and notes.
Jean Muriel Sovatkin was born on March 7, 1921, in Brooklyn, New York to Edward J. and Frances Sklar Sovatkin. Edward J. Sovatkin (originally naturalized under the name Sovatsky), an immigrant from Russia, joined his future father-in-law's surgical instruments manufacturing company as an office boy in 1902 and eventually worked his way up to president. He held several patents for surgical devices. Jean prepared for college at Packer Collegiate Institute. After her graduation from Smith College in 1942, she worked for Life magazine in London, New York, and Hollywood. She married Edwin de Haven Grosholz in 1943. The relationship did not survive the long separations caused by his navy service during World War II. They divorced in 1946. In 1947 she married Harvey Picker, a businessman who worked in medical manufacturing. Following the birth of their daughters, Frances and Gale, in 1949 and 1950, respectively, Jean began work as Director of Information for the Civil Defense Administration of Westchester, New York, County Government.
In 1953, in order to pursue her interest in international affairs, Picker began volunteering as a lecturer at the United Nations, interpreting U.N. goings-on to visitors. She held this position until 1961. In 1955, she collaborated with Eleanor Roosevelt to produce a booklet, "The United Nations and What You Should Know about It." In 1962, she co-founded the Interchange Foundation with Anna Lord Strauss. The Interchange Foundation produced informational and educational materials about the U.N. In 1973, Jean Picker compiled and published, through Interchange, a book titled Eleanor Roosevelt: Her Day.
In 1967, she was appointed to the United States National Commission for UNESCO. In the fall of 1968, she served as an Alternate United States Representative to the Third Committee of the Twenty-third General Assembly of the United Nations. The Third Committee is responsible for Social, Humanitarian, and Cultural issues. In February 1969, President Richard Nixon appointed Jean Picker United States Representative on the United Nations Commission for Social Development. She was Special Advisor to the United States delegation to numerous sessions of the Economic and Social Council (ECOSOC) as well as the General Assembly. She ceased work in her official U.N. position in 1977, but remained active in civic organizations promoting the U.N.
She was a member of the Committee of Correspondence, a communications network that aimed to bring women's clubs around the world into closer contact. She served on numerous boards, including the Foreign Policy Association, the United Nations Association of the United States and several bank boards. She also served in leadership capacities for several colleges and universities, including Fisk University, Smith College, Friends World College, Columbia University, Colgate University, and Hampshire College. Among other awards, she was given the Smith College Medal in 1977. She was the first recipient of the first United Nations Eleanor Roosevelt Leadership Award in 1988 in honor of her commitment to international cooperation.
She resided on Edgewater Point in Mamaroneck, New York for many years. She died at the age of 69 in Camden, Maine in May 1990. Jean Picker endowed Smith College's Jean Picker Semester-in-Washington Program in 1971. The highly competitive program "provides students with an opportunity to study processes by which public policy is made and implemented at the national level." In 1999 Harvey Picker made a gift to Smith College in honor of his late wife to establish the Picker Engineering Program to attract women to the field. It was the first engineering program at a women's college.
The Jean Picker papers consist of 18.5 linear feet and are primarily related to her professional and public life, dating from 1968-86. Types of material include correspondence, speeches, photographs, articles, reports, minutes, publicity, transcripts of interviews, invitations, and notes. The papers are arranged in four series:
I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS AND PHOTOGRAPHS
II. CORRESPONDENCE
III. PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES AND ORGANIZATIONS
IV. SUBJECT FILES
MEMORABILIA
OVERSIZE MATERIALS
The bulk of the papers date from 1968 to 1986 and focus of Picker's career with the United Nations and related supporting organizations. Major topics found throughout these papers include human rights, social development, youth, criminality, refugees and migrant workers, the rights of people with disabilities, multilateral issues, multinational corporations, economic problems, and arms control with the Soviet Union. With the exception of a small amount of correspondence, the papers reveal little about Picker's private life. Notable correspondents include Barbara and George H.W. Bush.
The Papers are open to research according to the regulations of the Sophia Smith Collection without any additional restrictions.
Jean Picker donated her Papers to the Sophia Smith Collection between 1984 and her death in 1990. Additional materials were received between 1991 and 2013 from Harvey Picker and his estate.
Committee of Correspondence (New York, N.Y.: 1952-1969)--History--Sources; International cooperation--History--Sources; International education--History--Sources; Journalists--United States--Biography--Sources; Women journalists--United States--Biography--Sources; Peace--Societies, etc.; United Nations--Officials and employees, American; Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962; Picker, Jean S.; Council on Religion and International Affairs; American Association for the United Nations; United Nations. Commission for Social Development
Related materials can be found in the Committee of Correspondence records in the Sophia Smith Collection and in the files of the Smith College Medal Committee and the Smith Centennial Study Oral History Project in the Smith College Archives. Information on Smith College programs funded by Jean and Harvey Picker, such as the Jean Picker Semester-in-Washington and the Picker Engineering Program, can also be found in the Smith College Archives.
- SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS AND PHOTOGRAPHS 1953-1997, 1 linear ft.
  This series provides an overview of the career and public life of Jean Picker. Newspaper articles, dating from 1943 to 1983, and autobiographical sketches (1968-83) document Picker's many positions and achievements. This series also documents Jean Picker's travel to China, awards, some general speeches, and charitable donations. Included is a copy of a Columbia University oral history transcript and a small number of photographs.
- SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE 1945-1986, 1.5 linear ft.
  The bulk of this series is general correspondence, primarily professional in nature, dating from 1968-85. It is arranged chronologically.
  A small amount of personal correspondence includes exchanges with several family members and friends including Emily Grosholz and long-time friend Rita Silberstein (Mrs. Alan Raphael).
- SERIES III. PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES AND ORGANIZATIONS 1952-1986, 15 linear ft.
  This series, which comprises the bulk of the Papers, consists of materials relating to the organizations and institutions that Jean Picker served. They are arranged alphabetically by organization. Types of materials include meeting minutes, educational publications, journal articles, correspondence, notes, speeches, and published reports. A significant amount of material can be found here relating to Picker's involvement with the Committee of Correspondence, Council on Religion and International Affairs (CRIA), United Nations, and the United Nations Association of the United States of America (UNA-USA).
- SERIES IV. SUBJECT FILES 1950-1985, .5 linear ft.
  This series consists of material compiled by Jean Picker primarily early in her tenure as a U.S. Representative to the United Nations. Picker's file names were retained and reflect the language of their time. The topics predominantly relate to social issues, such as crime, adoption, development, and youth. They are arranged alphabetically.
- MEMORABILIA 1968-1986, .25 linear ft.
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS 1936-1987, .25 linear ft.
- SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIAL AND PHOTOGRAPHS
  - Notes by Jean Picker regarding her papers, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Address lists, 1977-81, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Appointment books, planners, and calendars
    - 1968-81 (Box 1, Folder 3-19)
    - 1982-84 (Box 2, Folder 1-6)
  - Awards
    - General, 1980-88 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Honorary Doctor of Laws degree, The Medical College of Pennsylvania, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Biographical sketches, resumes, and news clippings, 1943-83 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Harvey Picker, 2008-12 (Box 2, Folder 9a)
  - Charitable donations, 1972-83 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Oral History, Columbia University, 1983-84 (Box 2, Folder 11-13)
  - Memorabilia, 1953-97, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Speeches
    - Packer Collegiate Institute Founder's Day, 9 Nov 1961 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - "Instant Diplomat," Mar 1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Texas Woman's University, 26 Mar 1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Surprise birthday party, 4 Mar 1956 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Travel
    - China
      - General, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Articles, 1972-78 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Speeches, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 21-22)
    - Photo exhibition, 1976-77 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Soviet Union
      - Guidebooks, 1963-64 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Report by Jean Picker, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, 1946-77, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
- SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE
  - General
    - 1968-76 (Box 3, Folder 3-19)
    - 1977-80 (Box 4, Folder 1-20)
    - 1980-85 (Box 5, Folder 1-20)
  - Family, 1972-80, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Emily Grosholz, 1981-83 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Rita (Silberstein) Stone [later Mrs. Alan Raphael], 1945-86, undated (Box 6, Folder 3-4)
  - Smith College, 1954-95 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Greeting cards, 1968-78, undated (Box 6, Folder 6-8)
  - Invitations, 1968-75 (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
  - Third party, 1968-76 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- SERIES III. PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES AND ORGANIZATIONS
  - African-American Institute: annual report, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - American Stock Exchange, 1977-78 (Box 6, Folder 14-17)
  - Bank of New York, 1977-80 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Coalition for Women in International Development, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Committee of Correspondence
    - Administration
      - General, 1953-67 (Box 6, Folder 20-22)
      - Mailing lists, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Minutes, Sep-Oct 1968 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence
      - General, 1952-63 (Box 7, Folder 2-9)
      - General (after closing), 1970-72 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Africa, 1966-67 (Box 7, Folder 11-12)
      - Latin America, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Special Mailings, Jan 1964-69 (Box 7, Folder 14-20)
      - United States, 1967-70 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Jacqueline van Voris, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Publicity, 1959-61, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Publications: Meeting Community Needs
      - 1965-66 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - 1966-68 (Box 8, Folder 1-4)
  - Cosmopolitan Club, Board of Governors, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Council on Religion and International Affairs (CRIA)
    - Statement of Purpose and bylaws, 1915-74 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Legal, Internal Revenue Service, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and financial contributions, 1973-78 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Notes, 1973-77 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Financial, 1972-77 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Board of Trustees
      - Members, 1973-75 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Annual and semi-annual meetings, Jun 1973-Jan 1978 (Box 8, Folder 12-23)
    - Executive committee: minutes, 1974-76 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Program committee: minutes, 1974-77 (Box 9, Folder 2-3)
    - Worldview Symposium: "Restructuring Patriotism Today," Jan 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Reports and articles evaluating CRIA, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Division of Educational Programs, Continuing education, and Ministry, 1974-77 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Consultation reports, 1973-76 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Kenneth Thompson program proposal, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Speech by Admiral Harry D. Train, 13 Apr 1982 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      [see also Foreign Policy Association]
    - Aspen Institute policy paper: "Human Requirements, Supply Levels, and Outer Bounds: A Framework for Thinking about the Planetary Bargain," 1975 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Worldview articles for discussion, Oct 1974- Oct 1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Carnegie Center for Transnational Studies
      - General and correspondence, 1976-77 (Box 9, Folder 12-13)
      - "The Nation-State and the Multinational Corporation in Lesser Developed Countries: Latin America," Sep 1973 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Corporate Consultation Program
        - Project proposal, 1972-79 (Box 9, Folder 15)
        - Reports, 1975-78 (Box 9, Folder 16-17)
        - Meeting, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Reports on Taxation, Employment, New International Order, Jul 1976 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - "Value Systems and World Food Crisis" meeting, 1976-77 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Centennial Observance Initiating Committee, Jun 1983 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Foreign Policy Association (FPA)
    - General and miscellaneous, 1971-76 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1972-77 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Financial
      - General, 1974-76 (Box 9, Folder 24-25)
      - Capital campaign, Jan 1985 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
    - Board of Directors: meetings, 1974-79 (Box 10, Folder 3-8)
    - Publications and papers
      - At a Glance, 1975-78 (Box 10, Folder 9-11)
      - "UN at Thirty-Five," Wallace Irwin Jr., Oct 1979 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - "Dealing with China: An American Dilemma" by Richard Baum, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - "China and America: Past and Future," Apr 1977 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - "America in International Perspective" by Marina Whitman, 2 Mar 1982 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Admiral Harry D. Train event, Apr 1982 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Discussion with Henry Kissinger's planning staff, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Presentation: "The Future of FPA" by Carter Burgess, Sep 1974 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Proposal: A National Council on Citizen Education in International Relations, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Foundation for Child Development: meeting of Board of Directors, 3 Mar 1977 (Box 10, Folder 20-22)
  - Franklin Books Program
    - Administrative
      - General, 1968-77, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - Board of Directors (Box 10)
        - Welcome Packet, 5 Dec 1968 (Box 10, Folder 24)
        - General
          - 1974-75 (Box 10, Folder 25)
          - 1977-78 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1970-78 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Speech on Iran, 15 Nov 1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Reports
        - History and current projects, Oct 1972 (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
        - Annual, 1970-73 (Box 11, Folder 6-8)
      - Bangladesh printing survey, Oct-Nov 1972 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Publications: The Franklin Newsletter, 1972-75 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Interchange Foundation
    - Bylaws, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Insignia, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Legal, 1960-73 (Box 11, Folder 13-14)
    - Financial, 1963-85 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Minutes, 1963-76 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence and telephone messages, 1970-81 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Publication: Eleanor Roosevelt: Her Day, 1974
      - Costs, 1973-74 (Box 11, Folder 18-19)
      - Agreements, 1972-73 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence
        - Orders, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 21)
        - Publisher, 1973-74 (Box 11, Folder 22)
        - Response, 1973-74 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Drafts
        - Foreword by Jean Picker, 1973-74 (Box 12, Folder 2)
        - Manuscript, 10 Feb 1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
        - Acknowledgement and reference material, 1973-74 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
      - News clippings, 1973-74 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Photographs, undated (Box 12, Folder 8-11)
  - Institute for World Order
    - General, 1974-77 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - World Models Project, 1968-72 (Box 12, Folder 13-15)
    - Media coverage, 1974-76 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Board of Directors
      - 1974-77 (Box 12, Folder 17-21)
      - 1978-79 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - "Reassessing American Values": public education program proposal, Sep-Oct 1974 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1973-79 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Grant Committee, 1972-77 (Box 13, Folder 4-5)
    - World Order Values workshop, 4-6 Apr 1975
      - General (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Reading materials (Box 13, Folder 7-10)
    - University Centers Program: criteria and progress reports, 1973-74 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - International Conference on Social Welfare, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - International Symposium on Social Welfare Responsibility, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - New York City Commission for the United Nations, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - New York Institute for the Humanities, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Organization for Economic Co-operation and Development, Jan-Feb 1971 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - United Nations Association of the United States of America (UNA-USA) (Box 13)
    - General
      - Notes, 1972-82 (Box 13, Folder 17-18)
      - Miscellaneous, 1970-84 (Box 13, Folder 19-23)
    - Administration
      - Bylaws and letterhead, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - Directory, Mar 1983 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Address lists, 1977-82, undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - Board of Directors
        - Membership, circa 1972 (Box 13, Folder 24)
        - Mailings, 1981-83 (Box 14, Folder 1-13)
        - Meetings
          - 24 Sep 1971-4 Mar 1974 (Box 14, Folder 14-21)
          - 17 Nov 1975-17 Nov 1980 (Box 15, Folder 1-21)
          - 16 Nov 1981-5 Dec 1983 (Box 16, Folder 1-7)
      - Board of Governors
        - Minutes and meeting materials
          - 1972-82 (Box 16, Folder 8-21)
          - 1983-86 (Box 17, Folder 1-14)
        - Review Committee, 1980-82 (Box 17, Folder 15-22)
      - Staff meetings, 1981-82 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Committees (Box 18)
        - Finance and Budget, 1975-86 (Box 18, Folder 1-5)
          [see also: oversize]
        - International Cooperation Year, 1964-65 (Box 18, Folder 6)
        - Nominating, 1973-83 (Box 18, Folder 7)
        - Policy Studies
          - General
            - Abstracts of UNA-Policy Studies Panels, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 8)
            - Meetings, 1974-82 (Box 18, Folder 9-11)
          - Economic Policy Council (EPC)
            - Publications and press, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 12)
            - Panels
              - Illegal Immigration, 1981-82 (Box 18, Folder 13-14)
              - Industrial Objectives Panel, May 1982 (Box 18, Folder 15)
              - International Financial Institutions, Jan-May 1982 (Box 18, Folder 16-21)
              - North American Economic Area, Feb 1981 (Box 18, Folder 22-23)
              - Parents and Work, 1982-84 (Box 18, Folder 24)
              - Productivity, 1981-82 (Box 19, Folder 1-4)
              - US Trade Relations with Japan and Mexico, Mar-Dec 1982 (Box 19, Folder 5-8)
          - Parallel Studies Programs
            - Chinese-American Parallel Studies program
              - Beijing conference, May 1982 (Box 19, Folder 9)
              - China Council of the Asia Society: essays, 1982-84 (Box 19, Folder 10-13)
              - National Policy Panel to Study US-China relations, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 14)
              - Policy papers about Taiwan, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 15)
            - Japanese-American Parallel Studies program
              - Defense survey, 1981-82 (Box 19, Folder 16)
              - Memoranda, 1981-82 (Box 19, Folder 17-23)
              - Conference, Jan 1982 (Box 20, Folder 1)
              - The Japanese American Alliance: A Framework for the Future, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 2)
              - Future of the Global Economy, Jan-Apr 1985 (Box 20, Folder 3)
            - Soviet-American Parallel Studies program
              - Arms Control and Security Panel, Dec 1982-Mar 1985 (Box 20, Folder 4-8)
              - Bilateral Global Economic Issues, Mar 1984-Mar 1985 (Box 20, Folder 9)
              - Joint conferences, 1982-84 (Box 20, Folder 10)
              - Economics panel, Oct 1982-Feb 1985 (Box 20, Folder 11-19)
              - Funding proposal, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 20)
              - Articles by Tobi Trister Gati (Box 20)
              - "Soviet and American Behavior in Multilateral Institutions," 20 Oct 1978 (Box 20, Folder 21)
              - "The Soviet Union and the North-South Dialogue over a New International Economic Order," undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
          - Other Panels
            - Major Powers in East Asia, Oct 1983-Mar 1985 (Box 20, Folder 23-25)
            - Major Powers in East Asia, Apr 1985 (Box 21, Folder 1-3)
            - Multilateral Issues and Institutions
              - Draft: "American Interest and the UN," Donald J Puchala, Apr 1982 (Box 21, Folder 4)
              - Multilateral projects, 1982-85 (Box 21, Folder 5-6)
              - The Futures Group
                - "A Handbook for U.S. Participation in Multilateral Diplomacy," 1981 (Box 21, Folder 7-8)
                - "Negotiation, Multilateral Diplomacy, and North-South Relations," May 1981 (Box 21, Folder 9)
            - Multilateral Approaches to Arms Control, Feb-Jul 1982 (Box 21, Folder 10-12)
            - National Policy Panel on US-Soviet Relations, Jan 1981 (Box 21, Folder 13-14)
            - United Nations Capabilities in the 1970s, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 15)
            - The US, The UN and the Management of Global Change, Aug 1982 (Box 21, Folder 16)
        - World Federation of United Nations Associations, 1978-83
          - Mailings, 1978-83 (Box 21, Folder 17-19)
          - 28th-29th Plenary Assembly, 1981-83 (Box 21, Folder 20-24)
          - Bulletin, 1981-83 (Box 22, Folder 1)
          - Publicity (Box 22, Folder 2)
          - Correspondence with UNA-USA, 1982-83 (Box 22, Folder 3)
          - Other materials (Box 22, Folder 4-6)
      - Financial materials
        - Expense account, Sep 1974-Jan 1986 (Box 22, Folder 7-10)
        - Fundraising initiatives
          - General, 1977-82 (Box 22, Folder 11)
          - Proposal to Exxon, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 12)
          - Proposal to Carnegie Corporation: "Containing Local Conflict: Rethinking Multilateral Alternatives," 1984 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Intra-office memoranda
        - General, 1973-84 (Box 22, Folder 14)
        - From Jean Picker, 1974-80 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence from Jean Picker, 1970-86 (Box 22, Folder 16-17)
    - Field Office
      - Memoranda, 1981-82 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Council of Organizations, National Business Woman, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Corporate Council for International Policy, 1982-83 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Council of Chapter and Division Presidents
        - Correspondence, 1981-82 (Box 22, Folder 21-22)
        - "War and Peace in Iowa," Oct 1982 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Washington Office
      - General, 1980-81 (Box 22, Folder 24)
      - Report: "Congressional Influence on US-UN Relations," 1978 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Public Relations
      - Press list, undated (Box 22, Folder 26)